

# MAURO CONSOLANI

## **PROFILE**

Self-taught web developer and experienced HR consultant. Thirsty for challenges of any kind. I deeply enjoy working on projects with team-mates. I am extremely enthusiastic and self-motivated. Above all, I'm a very hard working professional.



Briggitenau, Vienna, Austria



Click to check it out!



mfconsolani@outlook.com



github.com/mfconsolani



26 years old



/mauro-consolani



Argentine/Spanish

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### WEB DEVELOPER

#### 4HAPPYDEVS (2020 - present)

- Frontend web apps development based on HTML5, CSS3 & Bootstrap4
- Backend web apps development based on Python (Flask)
- Deployment on **Heroku**

## HR MANAGMENT CONSULT.

### **Provincial Ministry of Education** (2019 - 2020)

- Management reporting and projects follow-up
- Personnel administration
- Customer service

## HR COORDINATOR\*

#### **Provincial Bureau of Administrative Modernization** (2017-2019)

(2018-2019)

- **Development** and implementation of a **performance assessment system**
- **In charge** of 5 team partners

## HR ANALYST

(2017-2018)

- Human resources **recruitment**
- Formalization of internal processes
- Development of internal **training program**
- Tasks management, internal communication and assessment of work environment

## **EDUCATION**

#### SELF-TAUGHT DEVELOPER

**Udemy, Edx, books and wherever knowledge lives!** (2019 - present) Check my website!

#### BA IN HUMAN RESOURCES

UCALP, Argentina (2014 - 2017)

## SKILLS

#### **TECHNICAL**

- Python
- HTML5 & CSS3
- Bootstrap 4
- JavaScript (in progress)
- HR Managment
- HR Recruiting
- Bilingual (English Spanish)

Jira

• Git & Github

• German Language (in pogress)

#### SOFT

- Self-motivated
- Problem-solving
- Methodical
- Teamwork

- Life-long learner
- Management
- Communication
- Integrity

## INTERESTS & MORE...

## WEB APPLICATION

#### Pasto a Pasto - Web App (2020 - present)

Pasto a Pasto web app is meant to measure the forage offer level for stockbreeding establishments to optimize their productivity. Driven by Scrum methodology, we were able to deploy the MVP after three weeks. Git & GitHub flow, Jira, team organization, team communication and logical creativity were the foundation stones for this project.

Check it out! www.pastoapasto.com.ar

# CRAFT BEER ENTREPREUNERSHIP

#### **ARCCADIA** (2017 - 2019)

Arccadia was built by four very close friends and myself. We started brewing 20lts. per month and reached a maximum of 400lts. per month. We **learned** about **administration**, production, **organization** and **business** but best of all, we **developed** a high **teamwork spirit**.